So, earlier one in this video we are going to set up our toaster, but before that here
some parts are remaining.
So, this was a post slash auth and then slash sign up, comma data, whatever the data
we had.
So, we are going to use that and now here inside we are going to set the things like
set locked user as null value.
So, before this we like how to use this error.
So, what we are going to actually do is we are going to just import our toaster.
So, import the toaster from the package that we have installed.
So, in the app.chs file, once again I think system is hanging.
So, in this app.chs file we are going to import our toaster.
So, toaster, this toaster is used in order to display the message like whether the message
is returning like a red response or green response.
So, now after this let us go to this auth store.chs, now inside of this we are going to import
our toaster.
So, import 01 second this some problem.
So, in the main dot sorry app.chs file this toaster component as you can see is like this
set in the last this is a self closing tag, so make sure to import and use it here.
Right.
Now, after this go to this auth store.chs and inside of this we are going to just import
the toaster import the toaster, we are going to use 01 toaster in order to display the message.
So, import toaster from react hot toast and after this suppose some kind of error message
comes like when you are log in to a particular like using your particular account and password
you are going to log in and some error response comes.
So, we are going to get that error response in form of a toaster.
So, set logged, logged user to set logged user to null.
So, you already have written that and before that what we are going to do.
So, toast.error toast.error we are going to display the message like the sign up is failed.
So, sign up failed please try again, please try again.
So, error is defined I never used why we are showing this it should be like this only.
That catches here and then error sometimes it happens ok.
So, we are going to see this later and also suppose we are able to log in.
So, in that case toast dot success and this in the success we are saying that sign up
successful alright now there should be no issues if you restart the VS code this this kind
of errors will be gone ok.
So, now we have implemented the toast now let us get back to the sign up page.
So, the main thing here is components we have this sign up page and then the sign up page
will have some like like this only login page now bar sign up I have set up all of these.
So, in a minute I am going to set up all of that and we have to return back ok.